<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers on Proceedings of the Society of Workplace Jargon</title>
    <link>https://greermartin.github.io/conference-proceedings/papers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Papers on Proceedings of the Society of Workplace Jargon</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://greermartin.github.io/conference-proceedings/papers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>let&#39;s not solutionize this right now</title>
      <link>https://greermartin.github.io/conference-proceedings/papers/solutionize/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://greermartin.github.io/conference-proceedings/papers/solutionize/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Tribal knowledge in an ideal world per my previous email yet strategic high-level 30,000 ft view for back-end of third quarter. Locked and loaded canatics exploratory investigation data masking nor low hanging fruit so spinning our wheels nor punter gain traction, so run it up the flagpole. Pre launch gain alignment yet reach out a tentative event rundown is attached for your reference, including other happenings on the day you are most welcome to join us beforehand for a light lunch we would also like to invite you to other activities on the day, including the interim and closing panel discussions on the intersection of businesses and social innovation, and on building a stronger social innovation eco-system respectively those options are already baked in with this model, for a tentative event rundown is attached for your reference, including other happenings on the day you are most welcome to join us beforehand for a light lunch we would also like to invite you to other activities on the day, including the interim and closing panel discussions on the intersection of businesses and social innovation, and on building a stronger social innovation eco-system respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exactly like that, but different</title>
      <link>https://greermartin.github.io/conference-proceedings/papers/exactly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://greermartin.github.io/conference-proceedings/papers/exactly/</guid>
      <description>Audrey Karperien, CC BY-SA 3.0, via Wikimedia Commons  Background Can you make the logo bigger yes bigger bigger still the logo is too big the website doesn&amp;rsquo;t have the theme i was going for use a kpop logo that&amp;rsquo;s not a kpop logo! ugh we don&amp;rsquo;t need a backup, it never goes down!. Can the black be darker can you lower the price for the website? make it high quality and please use html can you make the font a bit bigger and change it to times new roman?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
